Magarik, Larry Scovill Retiree Health Insurance Ligation in Brass Valley Files 6361
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Larry Magarik Scovill Retiree Health Insurance Ligation in Brass Valley Files
1985-1988
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Magarik, Larry
Scovill Manufacturing Company
Zotto, Theodore
6361
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records.
8234286
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, August 21, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 07, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Magarik, Larry; Zotto, Theodore; Scovill Manufacturing Company
8234286
- Zotto v. Scovill Volume no.1 [folder 1 of 2], 1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Zotto v. Scovill Volume no.1 [folder 2 of 2], 1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Zotto v. Scovill Volume no.2 [folder 1 of 2], 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Zotto v. Scovill Volume no.2 [folder 2 of 2], 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Zotto v. Scovill Volume no.3 [folder 1 of 2], 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Zotto v. Scovill Volume no.3 [folder 2 of 2], 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Zotto v. Scovill Binder no.1: Preliminary Injection Proceedings [folder 1 of 2], 1985 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Zotto v. Scovill Binder no.1: Preliminary Injection Proceedings [folder 2 of 2], 1985 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Zotto v. Scovill Binder no.2: Motion for Summary Judgment [folder 1 of 2], 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Zotto v. Scovill Binder no.2: Motion for Summary Judgment [folder 2 of 2], 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Zotto v. Scovill Binder no.3: Class B Motion, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Zotto v. Scovill Binder no.4: Motion to Strike Jury Trial [folder 1 of 2], 1987 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Zotto v. Scovill Binder no.4: Motion to Strike Jury Trial [folder 2 of 2], 1987 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Zotto v. Scovill Binder no.5: Motion for Prejudgment Attachment, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Zotto v. Scovill Binder no.6: Century Brass Case, 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Zotto v. Scovill Binder no.7: Discovery Notices, Motion to Exclude Emotional Distress Damages, and Miscellaneous Motions, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Zotto v. Scovill Binder no.8: Litigation Papers, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Zotto v. Scovill Binder no.9: Settlement and Final Order [folder 1 of 2], 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Zotto v. Scovill Binder no.9: Settlement and Final Order [folder 2 of 2], 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Zotto v. Scovill Binder no.10: Settlement and Final Order, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 20)